gci.net 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy | GCI

**GCI Privacy Policy**

_UPDATED as of September 27, 2018_

**The GCI Commitment**

GCI is committed to delivering quality, innovative communications services to our customers. From the time you sign up for GCI Services, as you use these services, and as we provide additional services, you entrust with us your information. This information enables us to provide and support services, and the ability to improve, develop, and market services and content to enhance our customers’ experiences.

Because your information is important to us, we use reasonable and appropriate technical, security, and procedural measures as a safeguard to mitigate the chances of loss, misuse, and unauthorized disclosure.

In this Privacy Policy, we describe your personally identifiable information, its use and our commitment to protect it, and how federal laws apply to the individual services used by you.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post the modified Privacy Policy to this page. Your continued use of our Services and/or Websites following the posting of any changes will mean you accept those changes.

**Scope of Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information generated, delivered, or collected through your use of the following services provided by GCI and our subsidiaries (“GCI”), individually and in any combination, as identified below (the “Services” or “GCI Services”):  GCI local and long distance, wireless voice and data, video, and internet services; United Utilities (“UUI”) local, long distance, and internet services; and Supervision video and internet services. This policy also applies to visitors to [www.gci.com](https://www.gci.com/), [my.gci.com](https://www.gci.com/mygci), and other GCI websites (the “Websites” or “GCI Websites”).

Information may be collected when you provide it directly to us, such as by signing up for service or registering a user account (for example, your contact and billing information) and when generated from your use of our Services (for example, network or service performance data, device settings, and usage data).

**Personally Identifiable Information (Personal Information)**

Your use of GCI Services will sometimes generate or deliver personally identifiable information, which may be collected in connection with those Services (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is data associated with you that (1) is not already publicly available and (2) specifically identifies who you are. The type of Personal Information collected, which may vary depending on your subscribed Services, may include such items as your ** ** state driver’s license/ID number, social security number, credit/debit card number, bank account number, or similar account information. Aggregate, anonymous, de-identified, or other information that does not identify who you are when used by itself is not Personal Information and may be used or disclosed by GCI. 

More specifically, when linked with the identity of a specific person, Personal Information includes:

  * _[Customer Proprietary Network Information](https://www.gci.com/privacy-policy#cpni)_  (“CPNI”) as defined below (such as the quantity, technical configuration, location of certain telecommunication services used, all of which may be linked to your name, address, and phone number);
  * equipment and technical information (such as data about your video equipment, computer hardware and software, modems, routers, device settings, computer and internet connections, including IP addresses, operating systems, browser types and other applications);
  * location information (such as data about your wireless device when it is turned on);
  * service usage data (such as minutes used, bandwidth used, cable box viewing data); and
  * information about activity on GCI Websites (such as IP addresses, web addresses of sites visited before and after visiting GCI Websites, and other statistical data about visits).

**Use and Protection of Personal Information**

We use this information for a number of different purposes, including:

  * To monitor and maintain performance on GCI networks and devices;
  * To develop, support, and deliver purchased products and Services, to carry out billing and collection, and to answer your questions related to these Services;
  * To deliver more relevant and tailored marketing messages regarding other products or services that may be of interest;
  * To enforce our legal rights, protect GCI, and protect our users against fraud, abuse, and unlawful acts; and
  * For other purposes we disclose to you when you provide your Personal Information, such as when you participate in surveys and promotions.

GCI is committed to protecting the privacy of your Personal Information. We maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative measures in place to mitigate the chance of unauthorized access to or improper use of your information.

Because no security tool can provide absolute protection, however, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information will not be subject to inadvertent disclosure through illegal or unauthorized acts by third parties. In the unlikely event of inadvertent disclosure, we will notify you as required by law.

In the course of providing your Services, GCI may share Personal Information with our affiliates, contractors, service providers, business partners, and other third parties we use to support our business and provide customers with Services. These third parties will be contractually bound to protect your Personal Information and prohibited from using such information for any other purpose. Subject to the above, without your consent, GCI will not sell, trade, or disclose Personal Information that would specifically identify a customer, unless and except to the extent permitted by law.

Under certain circumstances, GCI may be required to disclose Personal Information without your consent:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or other legal process, including requests by the government or regulators;
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes; and
  * If necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of GCI, our customers, or others.

In the event of a merger, sale, transfer, restructuring, or any other reorganization of some or all of GCI’s assets, your Personal Information may be transferred to a buyer or other successor.

**Information Not Covered by this Policy**

Our Privacy Policy does not cover any information you provide or convey directly to companies other than GCI, including services you may access or third parties you may interact with, in the course of using GCI Services. Those providers may have separate agreements, terms, and privacy policies that govern the collection, use, and further disclosure of the information you provide to them, which we encourage you to review. To the extent you provide Personal Information directly to them, such information will be subject to their respective privacy policies. For example, you may elect to access your Netflix account through GCI video or internet service. The information you convey to Netflix is not covered by GCI’s Privacy Policy.

You also may access third-party websites or services via your internet or wireless data connections, and in doing so, you may provide information to other entities. GCI’s Privacy Policy does not apply to this information.

GCI Websites may contain links to other websites, including those of third parties that act on our behalf as agents, suppliers, or providers and that may have their own privacy policies. You should be aware that your information may be provided or conveyed by clicking on a link to another company’s website or advertisement from our Websites.

_We do not control the tracking practices of third parties. We encourage you to consult the privacy policies of third parties whose services you use, as well as websites you visit and with which you do business to learn more about how those parties may use your information._

**Additional Privacy Policy Terms**

**GCI TV and Supervision Subscribers**

As permitted by federal law, GCI may use the systems for providing cable service to collect Personal Information ** ** necessary to provide Services to our customers and to protect against any unauthorized access to such Services. Such information may be disclosed without a customer’s consent when necessary to provide these Services or to conduct legitimate related business activities. (Personal Information does not include aggregate data or other data that does not identify a particular person.)

Under certain circumstances, GCI may also be required by law to disclose viewership data without your consent, such as to a governmental entity in compliance with valid legal process (such as pursuant to warrants, court orders, or subpoenas), but only after you have had an opportunity to contest the claim. Similar disclosure of viewership data to a non-governmental entity may also be necessary to comply with a court order, but only after you have been provided notice of such an order.

Also as permitted by federal law, GCI may disclose subscriber names and addresses for other purposes, such as to charities, marketing organizations, and other businesses in the form of mailing lists that do not reveal any information about your viewing habits or transactions made over the cable system. Additionally, GCI may, directly or through its service providers, combine your non-personally identifiable viewing activity with demographic and other information to provide GCI with audience analysis data. We may share this non-personally identifiable information with others for programming, marketing, advertising, and similar purposes. We will not provide third parties with Personal Information, unless we have received your consent, except as required or permitted by law. If you do not wish to have your information shared in this manner, please see “Your Choices” below. 

**Local, Long Distance, and Wireless Telecommunications Subscribers**

CPNI is a special category of information that includes individually identifying information about who, when, and where you call, how much you spend on local, long distance, and wireless telecommunications services, which service plans you use, and information appearing on your bill regarding the type of services and features used, and it is protected by federal law. GCI does not sell or provide CPNI to any third parties. Under certain circumstances, GCI may be required to disclose CPNI without your consent, such as to comply with any laws, court orders, or subpoenas.

Within GCI, we use CPNI for billing purposes, to provide and change GCI Services, to contact customers for account service issues, and to provide information about other GCI products or Services that may be of interest. You have a choice about whether or not GCI shares your CPNI within our family of companies to create marketing offers regarding our other Services.

For wireless subscribers, GCI and GCI’s mobile applications primarily use location data (information about the location of your wireless device) to enable and support mobile and data Services and to provide 911 emergency services. Other third party mobile applications may also ask for your permission to use your location data for additional purposes. Please consult the respective policies of these third parties to learn more about their privacy practices.

**Tracking and Interest-Based Advertising**

Information about browser activity may be used in order to maintain and improve GCI’s network, Websites, and content performance. In particular, when you browse GCI Websites, we may collect information about your device and your visit (such as your IP address, browser type, device settings, and other statistical information). We use such information for operational purposes, as well as to help tailor advertisements to better match your interests and to deliver more relevant marketing messages on our Websites, via e-mail, or via other GCI Services and devices.

We may also use third parties to implement services to deliver advertisements about products and services, including GCI products and Services, on other websites, mobile websites, applications, and widgets. We or our third-party vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to collect information and deliver these ads based on your previous visits to GCI’s Websites. These third parties may also collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services.  They may use persistent identifiers to track your internet usage across other websites in their networks beyond the Websites, and data collected from a particular device that you use may be used with another computer or device that is linked to the browser or device on which that data was collected. While we do not knowingly provide these entities with information that personally identifies you, such third parties may, with sufficient data from other sources, be able to personally identify you, unknown to us. 

Many of the third-party advertisers that place tracking tools on our Websites are members of programs that offer you additional choices regarding the collection and use of your information. You can learn more about the options available to limit these third parties’ collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://youradchoices.com/about), as well as the webpages for [Facebook’s ad preferences tool](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/) and [Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

We may also use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc., and other third-party analytics services on our Websites. These analytics providers use cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with and use the Websites, compile reports on the Websites’ activity, and provide other services related to activity on and usage of the Websites. The technologies used by the analytics providers may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and any referring website. The Websites do not use the analytics services to gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=ZZ). To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of tracking of analytics by Google, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). 

Please note that opting out of advertising networks services does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using our Websites or on other websites, nor will it prevent the receipt of interest-based advertising from third parties that do not participate in these programs. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising conducted through participating networks, as provided by their policies and choice mechanisms. Your browser or device may include “Do Not Track” functionality. Our information collection, disclosure practices, and the choices that we provide, will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.

In addition, our Websites may use a technology that allows us to record mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling, and text keyed into website forms. This information does not include bank details or other sensitive financial information from our online payment forms. This data helps us improve our Websites’ usability. It may also be stored and used for aggregated and statistical reporting.

**Location Information**

When you visit our Websites or use our mobile applications, we may request information about your location. This location information allows us to provide location-based services, such as presenting you with a low bandwidth version of our Websites, tailoring advertising for you based on your location, and customizing the content that is displayed. In order to access certain video Services from your mobile device, you may also be required to share your device’s location information with us, which enables GCI to determine the programming content available to you in your location.

If you prefer not to share your location, you may do so in the settings of your browser or on your device. Please note that by opting out of sharing location data, your access to some Services may be limited or eliminated.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

GCI is concerned about the safety and privacy of all our users, particularly children. Minors cannot become GCI subscribers, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13 without parental consent. If we learn we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13 without such consent, we will delete such information.

For information regarding safety and controls related to GCI’s cable service, please view [GCI TV Parental Controls](https://www.gci.com/support/support-articles/tv_parental-controls).

**Your Choices and Control**

GCI is committed to protecting your privacy and offers the following choices to help manage the use of your customer information, including Personal Information. For questions about the choices described below, you may reach Customer Service at [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com) or via phone at (907) 265-5400 (Alaska) or toll-free at 1-800-800-4800. (Please note that the selections described below will not apply to customer-service or account-related notifications for your current subscribed GCI products or Services.)

**Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI)**

You may decline to receive offers for other GCI Services based on your CPNI, and your decision to do so will not affect the provision of any Services to which you currently subscribe. To opt out of this type of marketing, please e-mail your request to [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com) by including your (1) name, (2) home address, (3) home telephone number including area code, (4) Service number including area code, (5) Service billing address, and (6) Service account number. You may also send your request in writing via U.S. Mail to:

Attn: Customer Service  
2550 Denali Street, Suite 1000  
Anchorage, Alaska 99503

GCI will honor your opt-out request until affirmatively told otherwise.

**Mailing List**

If you do not want your name and address shared with third parties for “mailing list” purposes as described above in this notice, please contact customer service at (907) 265-5400 (Alaska) or toll-free at 1-800-800-4800.

**E-mail**

If you do not wish to receive marketing information via e-mail, you may opt out by following the “unsubscribe” instructions included in the e-mail message.

**Viewership Data**

If you do not want your non-personally identifiable viewership data combined with demographic or other similar information and shared with unaffiliated third parties, you may opt-out by sending an e-mail to [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com) (1) with “Viewership Data” in the subject line and (2) your name and GCI Service account number in the e-mail. 

**Phone**

GCI maintains an internal Do Not Call List to limit telemarketing at your request. To be added to this list, please contact Customer Service. To limit general telemarketing inquiries, you can also add your wireline or wireless telephone number free of charge to the Federal Trade Commission’s National Do Not Call Registry by visiting and following the instructions at [https://www.donotcall.gov](https://www.donotcall.gov/). (Please note that registration with the federal registry alone will not exclude calls from GCI, which is permitted under law to make calls to customers with whom it has an established business relationship.)

**Text**

If you would like to stop receiving marketing text messages, please contact Customer Service at (907) 265-5400 (Alaska) or toll-free at 1-800-800-4800.

**Access to Your GCI Personal Information**

GCI honors requests from customers for their own account information (such as name, address, or billing information). Please contact Customer Service, and we will correct any such information that may be inaccurate. GCI TV subscribers, upon request, may also review their Personal Information during regular business hours once GCI has been given a reasonable period of time to locate and prepare the information for review.

**Questions or Comments**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com).

_To access the Terms and Conditions applicable to specific GCI Services, please click  [here](https://www.gci.com/about/terms-conditions)._

Last Modified: 9/27/2018

**GCI Privacy Policy**

_UPDATED as of September 27, 2018_

**The GCI Commitment**

GCI is committed to delivering quality, innovative communications services to our customers. From the time you sign up for GCI Services, as you use these services, and as we provide additional services, you entrust with us your information. This information enables us to provide and support services, and the ability to improve, develop, and market services and content to enhance our customers’ experiences.

Because your information is important to us, we use reasonable and appropriate technical, security, and procedural measures as a safeguard to mitigate the chances of loss, misuse, and unauthorized disclosure.

In this Privacy Policy, we describe your personally identifiable information, its use and our commitment to protect it, and how federal laws apply to the individual services used by you.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post the modified Privacy Policy to this page. Your continued use of our Services and/or Websites following the posting of any changes will mean you accept those changes.

**Scope of Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information generated, delivered, or collected through your use of the following services provided by GCI and our subsidiaries (“GCI”), individually and in any combination, as identified below (the “Services” or “GCI Services”):  GCI local and long distance, wireless voice and data, video, and internet services; United Utilities (“UUI”) local, long distance, and internet services; and Supervision video and internet services. This policy also applies to visitors to [www.gci.com](https://www.gci.com/), [my.gci.com](https://www.gci.com/mygci), and other GCI websites (the “Websites” or “GCI Websites”).

Information may be collected when you provide it directly to us, such as by signing up for service or registering a user account (for example, your contact and billing information) and when generated from your use of our Services (for example, network or service performance data, device settings, and usage data).

**Personally Identifiable Information (Personal Information)**

Your use of GCI Services will sometimes generate or deliver personally identifiable information, which may be collected in connection with those Services (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is data associated with you that (1) is not already publicly available and (2) specifically identifies who you are. The type of Personal Information collected, which may vary depending on your subscribed Services, may include such items as your ** ** state driver’s license/ID number, social security number, credit/debit card number, bank account number, or similar account information. Aggregate, anonymous, de-identified, or other information that does not identify who you are when used by itself is not Personal Information and may be used or disclosed by GCI. 

More specifically, when linked with the identity of a specific person, Personal Information includes:

  * _[Customer Proprietary Network Information](https://www.gci.com/privacy-policy#cpni)_  (“CPNI”) as defined below (such as the quantity, technical configuration, location of certain telecommunication services used, all of which may be linked to your name, address, and phone number);
  * equipment and technical information (such as data about your video equipment, computer hardware and software, modems, routers, device settings, computer and internet connections, including IP addresses, operating systems, browser types and other applications);
  * location information (such as data about your wireless device when it is turned on);
  * service usage data (such as minutes used, bandwidth used, cable box viewing data); and
  * information about activity on GCI Websites (such as IP addresses, web addresses of sites visited before and after visiting GCI Websites, and other statistical data about visits).

**Use and Protection of Personal Information**

We use this information for a number of different purposes, including:

  * To monitor and maintain performance on GCI networks and devices;
  * To develop, support, and deliver purchased products and Services, to carry out billing and collection, and to answer your questions related to these Services;
  * To deliver more relevant and tailored marketing messages regarding other products or services that may be of interest;
  * To enforce our legal rights, protect GCI, and protect our users against fraud, abuse, and unlawful acts; and
  * For other purposes we disclose to you when you provide your Personal Information, such as when you participate in surveys and promotions.

GCI is committed to protecting the privacy of your Personal Information. We maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative measures in place to mitigate the chance of unauthorized access to or improper use of your information.

Because no security tool can provide absolute protection, however, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information will not be subject to inadvertent disclosure through illegal or unauthorized acts by third parties. In the unlikely event of inadvertent disclosure, we will notify you as required by law.

In the course of providing your Services, GCI may share Personal Information with our affiliates, contractors, service providers, business partners, and other third parties we use to support our business and provide customers with Services. These third parties will be contractually bound to protect your Personal Information and prohibited from using such information for any other purpose. Subject to the above, without your consent, GCI will not sell, trade, or disclose Personal Information that would specifically identify a customer, unless and except to the extent permitted by law.

Under certain circumstances, GCI may be required to disclose Personal Information without your consent:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or other legal process, including requests by the government or regulators;
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes; and
  * If necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of GCI, our customers, or others.

In the event of a merger, sale, transfer, restructuring, or any other reorganization of some or all of GCI’s assets, your Personal Information may be transferred to a buyer or other successor.

**Information Not Covered by this Policy**

Our Privacy Policy does not cover any information you provide or convey directly to companies other than GCI, including services you may access or third parties you may interact with, in the course of using GCI Services. Those providers may have separate agreements, terms, and privacy policies that govern the collection, use, and further disclosure of the information you provide to them, which we encourage you to review. To the extent you provide Personal Information directly to them, such information will be subject to their respective privacy policies. For example, you may elect to access your Netflix account through GCI video or internet service. The information you convey to Netflix is not covered by GCI’s Privacy Policy.

You also may access third-party websites or services via your internet or wireless data connections, and in doing so, you may provide information to other entities. GCI’s Privacy Policy does not apply to this information.

GCI Websites may contain links to other websites, including those of third parties that act on our behalf as agents, suppliers, or providers and that may have their own privacy policies. You should be aware that your information may be provided or conveyed by clicking on a link to another company’s website or advertisement from our Websites.

_We do not control the tracking practices of third parties. We encourage you to consult the privacy policies of third parties whose services you use, as well as websites you visit and with which you do business to learn more about how those parties may use your information._

**Additional Privacy Policy Terms**

**GCI TV and Supervision Subscribers**

As permitted by federal law, GCI may use the systems for providing cable service to collect Personal Information ** ** necessary to provide Services to our customers and to protect against any unauthorized access to such Services. Such information may be disclosed without a customer’s consent when necessary to provide these Services or to conduct legitimate related business activities. (Personal Information does not include aggregate data or other data that does not identify a particular person.)

Under certain circumstances, GCI may also be required by law to disclose viewership data without your consent, such as to a governmental entity in compliance with valid legal process (such as pursuant to warrants, court orders, or subpoenas), but only after you have had an opportunity to contest the claim. Similar disclosure of viewership data to a non-governmental entity may also be necessary to comply with a court order, but only after you have been provided notice of such an order.

Also as permitted by federal law, GCI may disclose subscriber names and addresses for other purposes, such as to charities, marketing organizations, and other businesses in the form of mailing lists that do not reveal any information about your viewing habits or transactions made over the cable system. Additionally, GCI may, directly or through its service providers, combine your non-personally identifiable viewing activity with demographic and other information to provide GCI with audience analysis data. We may share this non-personally identifiable information with others for programming, marketing, advertising, and similar purposes. We will not provide third parties with Personal Information, unless we have received your consent, except as required or permitted by law. If you do not wish to have your information shared in this manner, please see “Your Choices” below. 

**Local, Long Distance, and Wireless Telecommunications Subscribers**

CPNI is a special category of information that includes individually identifying information about who, when, and where you call, how much you spend on local, long distance, and wireless telecommunications services, which service plans you use, and information appearing on your bill regarding the type of services and features used, and it is protected by federal law. GCI does not sell or provide CPNI to any third parties. Under certain circumstances, GCI may be required to disclose CPNI without your consent, such as to comply with any laws, court orders, or subpoenas.

Within GCI, we use CPNI for billing purposes, to provide and change GCI Services, to contact customers for account service issues, and to provide information about other GCI products or Services that may be of interest. You have a choice about whether or not GCI shares your CPNI within our family of companies to create marketing offers regarding our other Services.

For wireless subscribers, GCI and GCI’s mobile applications primarily use location data (information about the location of your wireless device) to enable and support mobile and data Services and to provide 911 emergency services. Other third party mobile applications may also ask for your permission to use your location data for additional purposes. Please consult the respective policies of these third parties to learn more about their privacy practices.

**Tracking and Interest-Based Advertising**

Information about browser activity may be used in order to maintain and improve GCI’s network, Websites, and content performance. In particular, when you browse GCI Websites, we may collect information about your device and your visit (such as your IP address, browser type, device settings, and other statistical information). We use such information for operational purposes, as well as to help tailor advertisements to better match your interests and to deliver more relevant marketing messages on our Websites, via e-mail, or via other GCI Services and devices.

We may also use third parties to implement services to deliver advertisements about products and services, including GCI products and Services, on other websites, mobile websites, applications, and widgets. We or our third-party vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to collect information and deliver these ads based on your previous visits to GCI’s Websites. These third parties may also collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services.  They may use persistent identifiers to track your internet usage across other websites in their networks beyond the Websites, and data collected from a particular device that you use may be used with another computer or device that is linked to the browser or device on which that data was collected. While we do not knowingly provide these entities with information that personally identifies you, such third parties may, with sufficient data from other sources, be able to personally identify you, unknown to us. 

Many of the third-party advertisers that place tracking tools on our Websites are members of programs that offer you additional choices regarding the collection and use of your information. You can learn more about the options available to limit these third parties’ collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://youradchoices.com/about), as well as the webpages for [Facebook’s ad preferences tool](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/) and [Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

We may also use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc., and other third-party analytics services on our Websites. These analytics providers use cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with and use the Websites, compile reports on the Websites’ activity, and provide other services related to activity on and usage of the Websites. The technologies used by the analytics providers may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and any referring website. The Websites do not use the analytics services to gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=ZZ). To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of tracking of analytics by Google, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). 

Please note that opting out of advertising networks services does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using our Websites or on other websites, nor will it prevent the receipt of interest-based advertising from third parties that do not participate in these programs. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising conducted through participating networks, as provided by their policies and choice mechanisms. Your browser or device may include “Do Not Track” functionality. Our information collection, disclosure practices, and the choices that we provide, will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.

In addition, our Websites may use a technology that allows us to record mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling, and text keyed into website forms. This information does not include bank details or other sensitive financial information from our online payment forms. This data helps us improve our Websites’ usability. It may also be stored and used for aggregated and statistical reporting.

**Location Information**

When you visit our Websites or use our mobile applications, we may request information about your location. This location information allows us to provide location-based services, such as presenting you with a low bandwidth version of our Websites, tailoring advertising for you based on your location, and customizing the content that is displayed. In order to access certain video Services from your mobile device, you may also be required to share your device’s location information with us, which enables GCI to determine the programming content available to you in your location.

If you prefer not to share your location, you may do so in the settings of your browser or on your device. Please note that by opting out of sharing location data, your access to some Services may be limited or eliminated.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

GCI is concerned about the safety and privacy of all our users, particularly children. Minors cannot become GCI subscribers, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13 without parental consent. If we learn we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13 without such consent, we will delete such information.

For information regarding safety and controls related to GCI’s cable service, please view [GCI TV Parental Controls](https://www.gci.com/support/support-articles/tv_parental-controls).

**Your Choices and Control**

GCI is committed to protecting your privacy and offers the following choices to help manage the use of your customer information, including Personal Information. For questions about the choices described below, you may reach Customer Service at [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com) or via phone at (907) 265-5400 (Alaska) or toll-free at 1-800-800-4800. (Please note that the selections described below will not apply to customer-service or account-related notifications for your current subscribed GCI products or Services.)

**Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI)**

You may decline to receive offers for other GCI Services based on your CPNI, and your decision to do so will not affect the provision of any Services to which you currently subscribe. To opt out of this type of marketing, please e-mail your request to [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com) by including your (1) name, (2) home address, (3) home telephone number including area code, (4) Service number including area code, (5) Service billing address, and (6) Service account number. You may also send your request in writing via U.S. Mail to:

Attn: Customer Service  
2550 Denali Street, Suite 1000  
Anchorage, Alaska 99503

GCI will honor your opt-out request until affirmatively told otherwise.

**Mailing List**

If you do not want your name and address shared with third parties for “mailing list” purposes as described above in this notice, please contact customer service at (907) 265-5400 (Alaska) or toll-free at 1-800-800-4800.

**E-mail**

If you do not wish to receive marketing information via e-mail, you may opt out by following the “unsubscribe” instructions included in the e-mail message.

**Viewership Data**

If you do not want your non-personally identifiable viewership data combined with demographic or other similar information and shared with unaffiliated third parties, you may opt-out by sending an e-mail to [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com) (1) with “Viewership Data” in the subject line and (2) your name and GCI Service account number in the e-mail. 

**Phone**

GCI maintains an internal Do Not Call List to limit telemarketing at your request. To be added to this list, please contact Customer Service. To limit general telemarketing inquiries, you can also add your wireline or wireless telephone number free of charge to the Federal Trade Commission’s National Do Not Call Registry by visiting and following the instructions at [https://www.donotcall.gov](https://www.donotcall.gov/). (Please note that registration with the federal registry alone will not exclude calls from GCI, which is permitted under law to make calls to customers with whom it has an established business relationship.)

**Text**

If you would like to stop receiving marketing text messages, please contact Customer Service at (907) 265-5400 (Alaska) or toll-free at 1-800-800-4800.

**Access to Your GCI Personal Information**

GCI honors requests from customers for their own account information (such as name, address, or billing information). Please contact Customer Service, and we will correct any such information that may be inaccurate. GCI TV subscribers, upon request, may also review their Personal Information during regular business hours once GCI has been given a reasonable period of time to locate and prepare the information for review.

**Questions or Comments**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at [gciprivacy@gci.com](mailto:gciprivacy@gci.com).

_To access the Terms and Conditions applicable to specific GCI Services, please click  [here](https://www.gci.com/about/terms-conditions)._

Last Modified: 9/27/2018
